Subtitles and Timing Brought To You By The Gone With The Shirt Team @ Viki
♫ Love has to persist till the end ♫
♫ Looking at you, I don't wish to escape anymore ♫
♫ Your smile is too beautiful ♫
♫ I find it hard to breathe ♫
♫ Will you say, say 'I do?" ♫
♫ You appeared, in my life ♫
♫ Hard to resist, I can't resist ♫
♫ I will try, try my best ♫
♫ Just because you give me the courage ♫
♫ Courage ♫
♫ I'm willing to give my all to you ♫
♫ I just want to give you, give you happiness ♫
Customize Happiness
- Episode 33 -
The bags and shoes are her lifeblood. How can she sell them? You don't have any judgement at all.
I never would've thought I'd be in such a hole, and I'm suddenly back to not being free again.
I have been working in Beijing for ten years and this is what I have saved?
Sis, do you know that you have enough?
$500 isn't that much, but how much counts as a lot?
$500 is enough for us to live on for a month.
Must you have $100,000 to have money?
Moreover, you are not doing this alone. You still have me and Bei Bei.
And even Brother Zhan, too. Even though he didn't meet any of your eighteen conditions,
but... but he is sincere towards you.
You should know this is most important.
You must hold on to this happiness.
Don't keep thinking about useless things, working your hardest to have "enough."
If you want to put it nicely, you need to be strong.
To put it not nicely, it's a fool's errand.
Sis, everything is fine.
You still have me. What are you afraid of?
You have your little brother. I'll hold up the sky so it doesn't fall on you.
- Really?  - Don't worry. I need to.
Okay, let's have $40 worth of roast duck tonight. You can pay for it.
Hey, Bei Bei, don't we have to get to your Lamaze class?
- Yes, it's late. We should sleep.  - It's time for the baby to sleep.
- Where are you going?- Sing...
- a song for the baby later.  - ♫ Let's sleep.
So unreliable.
[Bank account]
There's no way to get past this.
Sorry, I can't sign this agreement.
Don't be like that, Old Xu. We already agreed. You can't just change your mind like that.
Didn't I already introduce you? With Zhan Wang's experience and skills,
he just needs to practice a bit, and that new guy won't even be able to catch up to him.
What I want now is results.
You said earlier, the racing team hasn't shown any results.
How could it not be?
That single-lap record at Goldenport was set by Zhan Wang, wasn't it?
That record? It has already been broken.
The person you want to collaborate with, is that Zhang Da Sheng?
There's no harm in telling you, I suppose. Zhang Da Sheng was the only Chinese racer in so many European championship races.
He is the best in China.
You can't criticize our decision to go with him.
He's young, vigorous, he's fast.
These are facts. You are a racer, too.
You should know this better. Time waits for no man!
I'm leaving.
Bastard. I don't believe that!
I, Gao Da Yong, even if I have to sell everything I own, will see this thing through. Let's drink.
Don't say anymore. The groceries are cheaper at the market.
We got so much stuff for $10.
Of course. You don't eat the food of the common people every day.
The groceries at the supermarket are more expensive. In future, let's buy them from the market.
Yes, the fish at the market are very fresh.
It's fresh and still alive.
Hurry, pick them up! My tomatoes, tomatoes!
Hurry up.
Thank you.
Thank you, Sir.
Saved $2 on the carp.
White cabbage, saved $5.
Liquid detergent, $8.
Hurry up. Half a kilogram of pork,
it's $8.50 less than the supermarket.
Dry cleaning bill...
Dry cleaning bill.
$85.
How am I still losing money?
Sis, you are too much.
Wearing custom haute couture to go shopping at the market.
- Isn't it your fault?  - Why are you blaming me?
If it wasn't for the ruckus you caused, would I be so poor?
There are no more cucumbers.
[Dear valued client. The new Cannage bag from Dior which you have ordered has arrived
Why must it be at this time?
We didn't have that many cucumbers in the first place.
I will cut some for you again.
- Brother Zhan.  - So how?  - The car is ready, but...
Who are you?
Hi. I came here to say hello.
Please get out from the car.
It's not a big deal. You can sit in my car, too.
No need. Thanks. Please get out from the car.
I heard you have prepared for a long time. I have been waiting,
but you don't have the right to compete in the race.
Say that again.
I said you don't have the right to compete in the race.
Brother Zhan, Brother Da Yong is looking for you.
[Notice of cancellation of Zhan Wang's right to race]
What does this mean?
They checked your records. You haven't competed in a race for two years.
They've already revoked your racing permit.
You don't have the right to compete. You need to take the test again.
Take the test again?
Three months. Level C.
The race would have already ended! What test do you want me to take again?
I will resolve this matter. Don't bother about this.
Looking for me?
Don't ask when you already know.
Is the result that surprising? You don't have a record of competing for the past two years.
Revoking your permit is completely in keeping with the regulations.
You went to so much trouble to make me return to racing.
Just so you could cancel my permit and teach me a lesson?
If you want to compete in the race, you need to take the test first.
Are you kidding me? Do you know there is no time now?
Zhan Wang, the "creme de la creme" of the racers will be at this race.
How can I prove that
you have the ability to compete?
You're also a top racer, but I can beat you anyway.
That was in the past but you can't defeat the young racers now.
Okay, give me another chance.
I will prove to you that I have the ability.
This is interesting. How are you going to prove it?
Is everything ready?
Hello, Director Cheng. This is Tian Xiao Ni.
You still remember me?
Director Pan, I remember you asked me to resign and join your company.
Why are you not answering my calls now?
What's wrong?
Hey, Brother Zhan. Um, my sis is on a rampage here at home.
The three of us can't handle it anymore. Can you help?
What's wrong with your sister?
I don't know. Come here first, okay?
Bye-bye.
What's wrong? Did you fight with them again?
Did Tian Liang tell you again?
No. In the past, I wanted you to resign
so that you could relax and enjoy your life.
Look at you now.
My goal is very simple. It's just to rely on my ability
to become more remarkable
and live a better life.
Why does God pull a prank on me when I'm almost there?
Everything has gone to zero and at the starting point again.
How could that be? Don't you have the talent?
You can start again. You have your family, friends and me, too.
These can't be bought with money.
Of course, I know.
These are the luxuries of life.
Can happiness give me money to support my family?
Thus, you should relax more.
Shouldn't you check
if you can lower your standards for happiness?
It's not that I haven't thought about lowering my standards,
but I have been applying this standard to myself for the past ten years.
You suddenly want me to give up everything I have
and deny the ten years of hard work?
If others don't understand me, will you, too?
I understand you and I'm not denying this, too.
I merely want you to relax more. You are in too much of a hurry.
Have you been out to have fun lately? Walk around somewhere, do something good for your heart?
Would I still have the mood to have fun?
Enjoying yourself is not a waste of time.
We should reassess our situation and our attitudes. Everything will be fine.
All these are logic. Anyone can understand this.
Don't talk about me. Let's talk about your race. Isn't everything going well?
I have my own ideas about the race. Don't bother about it.
- Okay, I won't bother about it at all.  - Xiao NI.
I was wrong. Sorry.
Look, you are making me anxious. I know you are concerned about me. Okay?
It's my fault.
I'm suddenly out of work and I don't know what to do.
I'm a little anxious, a little panicky. I'm not really used to it.
I know but do you know.
You are the most remarkable and strongest of all the women I have met.
I especially understand how you've worked so hard and suffered so much.
But don't forget,
you have me now. We are together.
No matter what obstacles you come across, I'll be the first one to block them from hitting you.
The days will better and they will be happier.
I believe it.
The password is your birthday.
- Why are you giving me this?  - It's my savings.
Starting from today, manage this card for me.
How can I take your money?
This belongs to us.
Hello, Aunt.
I can see that Da Yong is very busy for the past two days. He doesn't need to come every day.
To add further, my leg has improved. I can take care of myself.
He's not really that busy.
This time, he is really doing something and that is taking care of you.
If he doesn't treat you nice, call me.
If he shortchanges you with a meal, tell me and I won't let him off.
No matter what, Da Yong is a Director.
You make him come to my home to cook three meals for me. I really feel bad about this.
Don't make him come again.
Who says it's not suitable? It's a done deal.
Hello?
Don't say hello anymore. She has already hung up. It's my Mom checking on me?
I think that... you come here every day;
moreover, you are dressed like this in my home... it's...
It's a pretty good look for me.
I'm much better. I can walk now.
- Who's that?  - I don't know.
Don't move. You are a patient. Sit here.
Who's there?
Director Gao?
Jia Jia, you have a guest.
Xu Xin.
Gui Jia, I didn't expect you
to move that fast.
Don't leave.
Jia Jia, the guest is leaving. Why aren't you saying anything?
Mister Xu, it's dinner time.
I just cooked dinner for Jia Jia. There is still some in the pot. You must have already eaten.
Actually, Gu Jia and I have been together for a few days.
I have always wanted to find the opportunity to tell you.
I didn't expect to be caught by you that fast. Sorry about this.
Gu Jia, I'm here to tell you that
it's impossible for the both of us and that we should break up.
- My best wishes to you. Thanks.  - Bye!
- Xu Xin!  - Take care!
Gao Da Yong, what are you doing?
Gu Jia, do you like suffering that much? He's not worthy of you! What are you hitting me for?
Whether I'm willing or not, what business is that of yours? Don't think just because you cooked at my home for a few days that you are the master of the house!
Do you think I wanted to come here? My mom made me do it.
- Get lost!  - Fine!
Sis.
I saw that the weather is cold. I brought some clothes for you.
Do you think I can still wear those clothes?
Okay then. I'm leaving first.
Sis, don't be in such a hurry.
Look, here are some gifts from customers, skin products. I saved them for you.
No need. It's not like you don't know I don't like putting that stuff on my face.
Are you still angry with me?
Sis, seriously. I know you want to be good to Sister Xiao Ni.
You both are not blood related. Who's family and who's not?
I'm not one of those who differentiate between that. I'm talking about being reasonable.
- You said that Sister Xiao Ni...  - Yes, I know.
She brought me here. I shouldn't have done that to her.
It's good that you know.
Sis, you only know how to think on behalf of others. Have you ever thought on behalf of your biological buddy?
Do you know? Even if I let her have the position,
Bai Ruo Yan would never let her be the Boutique Manager, too.
Who is Bai Ruo Yan? We can't even defend ourselves against her.
Just because she sees someone suffering, she's going to give her a handout?
How is that possible? Let me tell you honestly.
When I was working in the office, I overheard Bai Ruo Yan and a few of her working partners talking
about blacklisting Sister Xiao Ni from this industry. You still don't get it?
No wonder. Xiao Ni recently wanted me to recommend work to her.
I already thought about this matter on your behalf.
I met a few customers today who are organizing a big design competition. They need another judge.
I went all out to recommend Xiao Ni for the job.
It's good if you can at least do this.
Look at you. You are just biased towards me.
Sis, no matter what, Sister Xiao Ni and I were colleagues. Isn't that so?
I can't see her in such a bad state.
She is facing difficulties now. I need to help her.
Okay, I'm thanking you on her behalf. I'm leaving first.
- Let's go. I will treat you to an expensive lunch. - I don't want to go.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Let me get it for you. Let's go.
Cui Cui wanted me to give this to you.
Cui Cui told you to give it to me?
Yes. Yesterday, she told me that she has regretted and she was wrong in the past. And not to be angry with her anymore.
She wanted me to tell you that this is from her and that she was wrong.
Enough, Gu Jia. It must be from you.
Don't worry. I won't blame her.
It's only just a job. If I have lost it, I can find another.
Bei Bei.
- Wait for me. Coming. - Open the door.
Move aside.
Tian Liang, what's wrong?
- What's wrong? - Everything's fine.  - Be careful.
What's going on?
Sister Xiao Ni, I'm very sorry. I really can't take care of him.
I asked him to just wash the cars, but he insisted on following me around to learn from me. I took my eyes off him for a second, and the car--
He was knocked down?
No, he got his hand stuck in the car door.
Lift his hand.
He only hurt his hand. Why did he faint?
I took him to the hospital to get it bandaged, and while it was being bandaged a patient passed by with a head covered in blood.
He took one look and fainted. He gave me a shock.
So he faints at the sight of blood? Bei Bei, why did he faint?
I didn't know, too.
I didn't know that he faints at the sight of blood.
It's okay. It's probably nothing major. You can hurry and get back to the garage now.
No, Sister Xiao Ni, I'm partly responsible for this, too.
It's not busy at the garage. There's no problem.
You should be at the training circuit with Zhan Wang now for the practice runs.
Huh? You didn't know?
Brother Zhan...
Thank you for sending me home.
How did you regain your consciousness?
Yes, how did I regain my consciousness? This is great.
By the way, Sister Xiao Ni, I'm going back to help them.
- Thanks...  - Stop there!
What are you both hiding from me?
Zhan Wang,
you have the experience, the skill.
But if you can't overcome your own fear, then it'll all be a waste.
I will definitely prove it to you.
Is that so? If you can't do it,
then you might as well go ride that bike I gave you.
If you can't do it, then you'd might as well go ride that bike I gave you.
Brother Zhan,
what are you doing? It's so hot and you are washing the car. Let's have a game.
I have been feeling tired lately. Just play by yourself.
What's wrong? Not in a good mood?
I'm just getting a sun tan. What do you mean?
Come off it. I know
your training for the race hasn't been smooth.
I have always wanted to talk to you and give you encouragements,
but I was afraid to say the wrong things to make it worse.
We are buddies. Just speak.
I will speak then.
Speak.
Frankly, it's not just only me. The rest of the buddies and Brother Da Yong, too...
We know you have run into problems but we couldn't help at all.
We could only just watch
but we really hope that, Brother Zhan...
About this,
I may disappoint everyone.
Brother Zhan, please don't talk like that.
Okay, go and play.
Brother Zhan.
What?
Which leg is longer?
What do you mean?
One leg is shorter than the other.
Were you injured in the past?
I used to race on a bike. I flew when I went round a bend.
I'll be deformed for life.
Okay, don't talk about this. You can even play basketball now.
I'm fine now, you can even barely say that my leg is agile.
But in here, there is a phobia.
I dare not look at a motorbike anymore.
Once I look at one, the scene of the accident will flash through my mind again.
It's just like it's right in front of me.
I'm at that turn again.
A collision and I'm flying.
My face hit something and I fell onto the racetrack.
My eyes were blurry, my mind was blank.
At that time, I was really very scared. I really thought I would die.
Since then, I have never touched a motorbike again.
Till today, thinking about it, I regretted making that decision.
But when I have recovered and if I go back to the race track again,
it would only take once, and I would get past this obstacle.
It has got to be better than how I am now, passing my days in a daze.
Enough. What do you mean by that?
Who hasn't made mistakes in their youth that come back to haunt them?
That's right. Everyone has dreams when they were young.
If one dares to go after that, it's an ideal. If one dares not,
then it'll forever leave a scar in your heart.
Brother Zhan, I was weak back then.
Brother Zhan, you can't be weak.
You are back.
Why are you here again?
Can't I come? I called you a few times but your phone was switched off.
Thus, I could only wait for you here.
I have been busy lately. Perhaps, my battery could have run out.
Let's go in and talk.
Come, sit. Did you wait a long time?
How's your training? I was afraid it would be tough for you.
I bought all these organic veggies for you. You need some nutrition.
I should give you my key so that you don't have to wait outside.
Are things going smoothly?
Yes.
Hey,
I wanted to say, one of my friends is a television host, do you remember?
Right now, he's doing a program about racing fans.
It's very popular. I already recommended you to be the participant. No problem, right?
You recommended me?
That's right.
What's wrong?
If you want to go on the program, it'll be good for your name recognition.
It will be easier for you to find sponsors in the future.
Da Yong was the one who has been finding sponsors for me.
Regarding this, you know my personality.
What if there's an awkward silence? Don't mess around. Listen to me, don't mess around, okay?
How am I messing around? I'm in charge of your publicity, right?
I know. Moreover,
I'm busy now with the training for the race. I'm worried and afraid now...
Zhan Wang, what are you afraid of?
- I...  - Your right to compete has been cancelled.
Why didn't you tell me?
You are here just because of this?
I'm your girlfriend and a member of your racing team.
Something so major happened. Why did you hide that from me?
Let me resolve this problem on my own.
The problem is you want to settle it on your own.
I know what you are afraid of.
You are afraid of the pressure from others. You are afraid you will disappoint them.
You are afraid you can't win,
so you're leaving yourself an escape route. You want to be a deserter, right?
Don't say anymore! Okay?
Am I wrong?
Yes, everything you said is right.
When everyone didn't want me to repair cars and wanted me to compete again,
I did it. You all wanted me to practice and recover my skills before the race,
adjust my situation, and I did it. I did everything, but what if I still can't win?
Zhan Wang, it wasn't because we wanted you to do it.
It's a question you have to ask yourself. Do you want to win?
Once I have thought it over, I will tell you.
Let me think about it first. Go back.
I say, Xiao Ni, you have been here for a long time and you have been silent.
It feels like you're here to use the free wifi.
Instead of coming here, why don't you just apologize to him?
Why should I apologize to him. I did that for his own good. I'm not going.
Do you know what your biggest problem is?
You are just too stubborn. Yes, you are always right.
There's a line from a poem, "Moisten all things softly without a sound." Got it?
You go up there and right away, you're all up in his face about it. What man is going to be able to tolerate that?
Whose side are you on, anyway? I did it out of concern.
It's just that he can't tell good criticism from bad.
In any case, it was your fault.
He isn't at fault, too? Do you know what the secret for a good relationship is?
It's trust.
The secret for a good relationship is trust now?
Your eighteen conditions are not important anymore?
If you didn't bring this up, I would have forgotten.
The last few days, I've been working so hard on this.
Look, I've made a detailed plan for Zhan Wang's future.
What do you think?
No. I say, Tian Xiao Ni.
You have gone overboard.
Zhan Wang is not a three-year-old kid.
What do you know? Men usually mature slower than women.
Do you know that saying? Women are mothers when they are young and men become kids when they are older.
Thus, whatever men can't think of, hear or do,
you should do it for them. This is what a smart girlfriend should do.
I only heard about this. Behind every successful man,
there is definitely a woman who is a busybody.
Looks like you've been spending all your time being obsessed.
A man's success and the schemes of the woman behind him
can't be separated. Many good relationships are not just about having a good companion. It's also about maturity.
This is ruining things through excessive enthusiasm.
Don't talk about enthusiasm, I'm almost out of it.
If he were to cancel his rights for the race, all our efforts would go to waste.
Talking about this, it's such a pity, too.
Two days ago when I did a television program,
I recommended Zhan Wang as a participant.
- What's the program?  - Matchmaking.
Match... you want my boyfriend to go on a matchmaking program?
Matchmaking is just a topic.
The people on that program are either releasing a new album or a new book.
They're all just there for publicity. Don't be so crude.
He doesn't even want to go on a motorcar program. It will be strange if he goes on a matchmaking program.
Do you want to go with me?
I'm not even an artist. Why would I go with you?
I'm not asking you to be the participant.
I'm asking you to do the wardrobe for the participants.
Aren't you having a financial crisis?
You are so reliable.
I will treat you to a lavish meal.
Of course.
But hasn't Gao Da Yong been taking care of your three meals lately?
I already told him not to come.
Why?
It's nothing. It's just that
he may not come again.
What's wrong with the both of you?
No...
I'm going to open the door.
Who is it?
Miss Gu Jia, I'm from Sea King. Director Gao asked me to deliver your dinner.
Please come in.
Please eat it while it's hot. I wish you good health as soon as possible.
Thanks.
You said he's not coming. Why is the food here?
Enough.
Subtitles and Timing Brought To You By The Gone With The Shirt Team @ Viki
Who...
It's me.
What brings you here?
I thought you were angry with me and wouldn't come again.
Would I dare to be angry with you?
About what happened that day, it was my fault.
I shouldn't have flared up and kicked you out.
Sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I was at fault, too.
It was between the both of you. I went a bit overboard.
So how was it? I personally ordered the menu for the food delivery for the past few days.
Do they suit your palate?
They were great. The meat and seafood are making me fat.
Seafood is expensive. Stop delivering them and focus on your business.
I guess you would be tired of eating the meat and fish.
Look at this. I'm here to cook light food for you today.
Fermented tofu with spinach. Sweet and sour lotus slices.
Celery and lily. Cold lotus root slices with sauce.
And also, cabbage and shellfish soup. There you go.
Actually, thanks for helping me cut through that tangled mess the other day.
He is definitely not worth doing anything for him.
Give me a hand.
But you said
it takes time to forget someone.
Thus, I was thinking I should pack up his stuff
so that I can slowly forget about him.
How's your packing?
It's almost done. He doesn't have much of his stuff here anyway.
Now, there's just the organic garden on the sundeck.
He personally planted them for me.
I was thinking plants are alive, too.
It would be too cruel.
Well, look. I'm gonna be busy cooking. There will be lots of greasy smoke.
Go and take a rest. I will call you when it's ready.
If you need any help, just call me.
No need. Go.
It's time to eat.
Coming.
Come.
It smells great.
Why didn't you follow the menu you set earlier? What happened to the fermented tofu and spinach?
I forgot to buy it.
And the celery and lily?
It wasn't fresh. I didn't cook it.
Then, what about the cold lotus root with sauce?
Well, if the lotus roots snap but the fibres stay connected, that's so ominous. (suggests that lovers will part but still long for each other) I couldn't make it either.
What did you cook then?
Let me tell you, these are Gao Da Yong original creations.
This one's called the "Breaking All Ties Stir Fry."
This one's called the "Go Separate Ways Small Fried Meat."
This one, it's called "Grow Old and Die Without Ever Crossing Paths Again Stew."
This one... this one is actually the cabbage and shellfish soup.
Try it.
Eat it.
Gao Da Yong!
Why did you pluck all of the organic veggies?
It was just convenient.
What do you mean? You are a murderer!
Do you know how hard I worked to plant those? How could you just pluck them like that?
Why are you so anxious? Didn't you plant these to be edible?
It's unreasonable to expect that you'd just raise them until they die, right?
What do you know? Those were for keepsakes.
What keepsakes?
Don't be unreasonable with me.
I come from a long line of cooks. I can't manage to feed you these fresh dishes,
and I can't manage my own mouth. What are you so excited about? Sit.
Sit down. I worked hard to cook these.
Eat a bite. I'm telling you, these organic veggies taste great.
Eat this. This is not bad.
What are you staring at?
Frankly speaking,
that rascal Xu Xin is nothing much but he's not bad at growing vegetables.
Pay attention to some organic farms in the outskirts.
If you want to eat organic veggies in the future, just let me know.
Okay, stop being angry .
Look and learn from me.
Put the food in the side of your mouth and chew with all your strength.
After you've chewed it thoroughly, then swallow it. Tomorrow morning, after you wake up, I promise,
you will forget how to write Xu Xin's name.
♫ Suddenly our eyes met, I only heard my heartbeat ♫
♫ But I pretended not to care, as though nothing happened ♫
♫ Time flies, every minute, look forward to see your smile ♫
♫ How long do I have to wait for us to meet again? ♫
♫ Why are we separated when we are obviously in love? ♫
♫ Why do we realize that all the mistakes shouldn't have been committed when we turn around? ♫
♫ If we love courageously, love courageously. Why does it leave behind so much pain? ♫
♫ Love courageously, I’ll customize the most beautiful love for you ♫
♫ If only time can prove true love ♫
♫ A moment becomes eternity, you will always know my dream ♫
♫ How many years have I longed for a bright future? You gave me too many heartbeats and touching moments ♫
♫ In the rain, embrace each other again ♫
♫ If we love courageously, love courageously. Why are we separated when we are obviously in love? ♫
♫ Why do we realize that all the mistakes shouldn't have been committed when we turn around? ♫
♫ If there’s a courageous love, and we love courageously. Why does it leave behind so much pain? ♫
♫ Love courageously, I’ll customize the most beautiful love for you ♫
♫ Love courageously, customize the most beautiful love for you ♫
♫ The most beautiful love ♫